Our first iCarly episode
as a couple.
And since we are doing
a Q and A with fans,
here's a practice question--
Who's my girlfriend?
Some gorgeous web star
who locked down the hottest guy
on her floor.
-(gasps)
-It's me. (chuckles)
Oh. (chuckles)
I have never been happier.
Well, except for maybe the time
my phone was on one percent
and then lasted the whole day,
like Hanukkah...
I'm kidding.
Never happier.
Me, too.
Can't wait to tell the world.
(giggles nervously)
Okay, frisky, down to business.
And we are live in five,
four, three, two...
Hey, and welcome to
Tuesdays with Carly,
our juicy Q and A we do
every Tuesday,
unless we forget like we did
for the last five Tuesdays.
As always,
I'll take this opportunity
to fold my laundry,
which I have also forgot to do
for the last five weeks.
Okay, first question.
"Carly, are you single?"
I think I know the answer
to this one.
Pass.
But in a nice way.
O... kay.
"Want to iCarly
and chill sometime?"
(scoffs) Prepare to be
disappointed, Mr. Question Man.
You mean watch
old episodes of my show
in a heavily air-conditioned
room? (chuckles)
I mean, that gets a big old
"yes, please."
Hey.
Here's a question from...
a totally real viewer.
"Are there any recent,
intimate developments
in your personal life
that you would like to share?"
Yeah.
Thanks for reminding me.
Mm-hmm.
I am completely,
totally head over heels for...
Aw, I'm already blushing.
...my new Smart Towel!
(chuckling)
I used to have to rely on
my dumb old eyeballs.
But when this baby vibrates,
that means I am bone dry.
Finally, dryness I can trust.
For 15% off, use code DRYCARLY.
I'm hurt,
but I also want that towel.
(giggling)
* I know *
* You see *
* Somehow the world
will change for me *
* And be so wonderful *
* So wake up
the members of my nation *
* It's your time to be *
* There's no chance
unless you take one *
* And the time to see
the brighter side *
* Of every situation *
* Some things are meant to be *
* So give your best
and leave the rest to me *
Carly. Carly.
Carly, I know you can hear me.
Can't talk. Too hungry.
Must eat sandwich.
But sandwich.
First talk, then sandwich.
I'm sorry... (sighs)
...but I don't want
to just blurt out
that you and I are together
on some Q and A
promoting the future of towels.
So, you're saying you want
to plan a big announcement?
Ah! Of course you do!
You're in the business of show.
Yeah. Totally.
That is exactly what I meant.
We just need a special idea.
The kind that takes a really
long time to think of.
Well, if you want special,
imagine the following--
A 40-slide
PowerPoint presentation
of which I have already made 37.
We can do the last three...
(quietly): together.
Fun.
(chuckling nervously)
Oh, here's a little something
for my favorite sweet tooth.
You know they can write
on cupcakes now.
Now that we've talked,
can I just focus on my sandwich?
-Yeah.
-'Kay.
* *
Spencer, you okay?
Of course, why?
-You said it was a matter
of life and death.
-And it is.
'Cause I've been dying
to show you something!
BOTH:
Oh.
I could be home doing nothing.
Shay What?! has always been
missing something.
-Blooming onions?
-Soap?
-ADA Compliance?
A bowl of pillow mints
by the cashier?
Did somebody say "possum"?
'Cause the answer's possum.
Oh, good.
I needed new nightmares.
Possum Secret Handshake?
I know this game.
It put Raccoon Simon Says
out of business.
My buddy Socko opened an arcade
and it closed a week later
'cause he realized he hates
loud noises and children.
He lost his life savings,
but I got a free possum.
(game whirs)
Who wants to have some fun?
I do.
I want to have some fun.
Totally poss-some.
Time to pay
so we can start to play.
(cash register chime)
(playful techno music playing)
My name is Janine.
What's yours?
Millicent.
So nice to meet you, Milli-cent.
I can tell that you are one
strong, smart young lady.
(giggles)
Go on...
Something really awkward
happened with me and Freddie.
Oh, good, you two finally
slept together.
Shut up.
He wants to announce publicly
that we're a couple,
but I'm not ready.
What's wrong?
It's the fedoras, isn't it?
No, those are growing on me.
Look, I just love being
in our cozy bubble.
It's just me and Freddie
and not the whole Internet
with their comments
that seem nice
but are actually sarcastic.
Good thing you don't live
for validation.
Come on, Carly,
you can't keep your
relationship hidden forever.
Or can I?
Like those men
with secret families.
You want to be like men
with secret families?
Harper, I just want
to stay in the bubble.
I know.
What if I show him
how great it is in here?
With an incredibly
romantic date.
In an incredibly romantic place.
Like a roof.
And what does one do on a roof?
Get free cable?
Have a picnic.
I'm gonna have
a super special picnic
on the roof of the Bushwell.
The place with the barbed wire
and the sign saying
not to go up there
or an alarm will sound?
That just makes it... forbidden.
Excellent job, Mill-i-cent.
With your coordination,
you could be a better pilot
than Sully Sullenberger.
I know that, but it's nice
to hear somebody else say it.
Totally poss-some!
Is that freaky possum
talking to you?
You bet I am, Har-per.
How do you know my name?
I'm always listening.
Now, why don't you
give me a try?
If you beat my final level,
you'll earn a hug.
Bitch, I can get a hug
anytime I want.
No problem.
Besides, you need rhythm
to play this game.
Oh, you will be hugging me.
(cash register chime)
(playful techno music playing)
I need your help.
Lose the fedoras.
They're growing on her.
Carly wants our couple
announcement to be special.
How many slides is
the PowerPoint presentation?
73 seven plus the three
we're gonna do together.
I can help you.
But we have to go now.
Now!
-Why?
-Because I'm quickly
losing interest.
Run, Freddie, run!
(shouts indistinctly)
* *
Hey, I thought
you were gonna tell me
what I need for my announcement.
Oh, right.
I lost interest.
Drones!
I said, "Drones!"
I know, I'm waiting
for you to say...
something else!
SPENCER:
Picture it--
Tomorrow night,
100 of these bad boys
in the Seattle skyline,
spelling out
"Creddie Forevvie"
and forming a beating heart.
Just like the opening credits
of Frasier,
but even more romantic.
That does sound romantic.
(gasps)
It's like a PowerPoint
presentation in the sky.
No, it isn't.
I'll handle the drones,
you handle my sister.
But with respect!
So you have 100 drones
just sitting around?
No, but I do have a credit card
and a Walmart  membership.
Free delivery, baby.
(chuckles)
-Ooh.
-And you know what?
Yes, I will add
a bath mat to my order
'cause I have slipped
so many times.
Okay, drones.
Yeah, let's do it.
Tomorrow night,
I will bring Carly
up to the roof to surprise her,
and livestream
the whole thing for the fans.
I mean, what could be
more romantic than a roof?
Our roof?
With the haunted water tank,
broken glass, and rat parade?
Oh, yeah.
The broken glass really catches
the light at sunset.
* *
(upbeat music playing)
I hope Tinsley doesn't mind me
missing her improv show.
That sounds important.
Nah, rich people are bad
at comedy.
I bet you're the funny one
in your relationship.
You land a joke
like Sully Sullenberger lands
a plane.
Go on...
Harper, it's my turn.
But I'm so close
to getting that hug.
I want that hug.
I need that hug.
Look over there.
It's Tinsley's improv team.
And they're asking for
suggestions from the audience.
What?! No!
Oh, no, you don't.
-Hey!
-Ahh!
Okay, shoving a kid.
Not my best look. (chuckles)
Please, sweet child,
have a turn.
But make it fast.
-Mill-i-cent, you're up.
-(cash register chimes)
I'm so glad you took my advice
and broke up with De-rek.
Now we have all day
to play together.
Wait, you broke up with Derek?
Yeah.
Janine thinks I can bag that kid
from Young Sheldon.
Wow, you're still playing this?
Is that why you didn't
come home last night?
Yeah!
Wait, what day is it?
I don't care.
Janine's the best.
She's like a therapy session
and a cardio workout
all rolled into one.
You should try it.
But you got to get
to the back of the line.
I'm busy.
And I refuse to make eye contact
with that thing.
I'm making a picnic for Freddie.
I just need a few supplies.
Like what?
Uh, you know, just utensils,
plates, napkins.
And a blanket and food.
But I have this killer basket.
Where did you get that basket?
It's yours.
(fanfare plays)
Forget college.
I'm going to Janine University.
Oh, we can be roommates!
Hey, I really don't think
that a grown woman should be
this obsessed with a game
recommended for nine-year-olds.
It's nine and up.
Harper, I think you should take
a good hard look
at your actions.
(exclaims)
Not my actions.
Huh. Does Carly have a point?
No, Har-per.
Ignore the girl
with the weird elbows.
If you leave,
I might get angry.
(deep voice): And you don't
want to see me angry.
(normal voice): Now,
who's ready for level 27?
Totally poss-some!
Hey, can I borrow a blanket?
What's going on in here?
Not sure what you mean.
Spencer, are you trying
to build a woman?
Just watching the game.
Did you see what happened
with the ball?
Kind of went wild...
'cause of the ball.
Why are you being so weird?
(Australian accent):
Weird?
What are you talking about,
mate?
I'm just here with my
miscellaneous aluminium drones.
Why are you doing your
Australian-hiding-something
accent?
Wait.
Don't tell me that Freddie is
planning on announcing
our relationship with a drone.
No.
With 100 drones!
I spent all afternoon
programming them.
No! Shut it down.
It's too late. Freddie's up
on the roof right now
connecting the transmitter
that sends the signal to--
Roof, transmitter...
Good. Bye.
SPENCER:
Carly-- Come on.
You forgot your basket!
Say nothing if I can eat
all the food.
Oh, I'm gonna Yogi Bear
the crap out of you.
You can't have any.
* *
Hey, there, Carly Nation.
We are livestreaming
for an exclusive announcement.
And just to fend off
disappointment,
it's not a PowerPoint.
There will be no slides.
Carly? Hey.
I was just about to
bring you up here,
but you beat me to it.
What a beautiful gesture.
Where's the transmitter?
Over there.
Wait, how do you know
about the transmitter?
(grunts)
I'm doing this for us.
-(screaming)
-No!
(screaming)
Stay... down!
Stop!
It's already dead!
(grunts)
Yeah, don't mess with
these delts.
Right?
These are delts?
I planned a sick drone display
to announce us,
and you're up here acting like
a dang roadrunner.
Did you have an extra
Capri Sun today?
-No.
-Mm...
Okay, fine. Yes.
But I just thought instead of
a big, flashy announcement,
maybe we don't announce
anything at all.
Wait, you don't want
to tell people about us?
Hold on, let me get my surprise.
It'll explain everything.
Well, maybe not everything.
It's just a picnic.
But it's a super cute one.
Hey, um...
I can't tell.
Is this a "push" or "pull"
situation?
You moved the chair?
Yes, it was in my way.
Now let me focus.
I'm trying to get this open.
It locks automatically...
from the inside.
-So you're saying we're...
-Trapped?
Yes.
Okay, let me just try
one more thing.
* *
Spencer, you're finally here.
Our friend Janine
just threatened us.
Which one's Janine?
The possum.
Oh, yeah. Ah!
Socko mentioned
this game got recalled
due to threats of violence
and an unsettling obsession
with hero pilot
Sully Sullenberger.
Lower your voice.
This is Janine country now.
I'll lower my voice...
in hell!
(growls softly)
Look if you're so worried
about it,
let's just go home.
Food sucks here anyway.
(chuckles)
(quiet beeping)
I wouldn't leave if I were you.
I know all your secrets.
And your credit card
information.
She could steal my identity.
I wasn't ready to start over.
Maybe you should.
I never loved
the name Millicent.
Or maybe I could call up
Tinsley and tell her,
(Harper's voice):
"I never want to see you again.
Also, I shop at stores with
the word 'barn' in the name."
(gasps)
Okay, we got to kill this thing.
I brought her in
and I'll take her out.
It's poss-o'clock somewhere.
JANINE:
Hey, guys,
I think we all said things
we didn't mean.
Let's just go back
to having fun.
Totally poss-some!
Don't listen to her.
Spencer, you haven't
played with me yet.
I have a special hug for you.
Special hug?
Maybe just a quick one.
(cash register chime)
(playful techno music playing)
(growling)
(screams)
Totally poss-some!
-(growling)
-Oh! Okay.
(groans)
Tell my ten kids I love them!
(grunts)
(voice fading):
Not... totally poss-some.
Wow, I always thought teamwork
was a crock, but--
She's alive!
-I've got this.
-(screams)
-(Janine growling)
-That possum was playing possum.
Oh, I guess that's where
the phrase comes from.
(voice fading):
I was your friend.
Millicent, you saved me
Oh...!
If it looks like
I peed myself in terror,
it's actually something
that's not bad.
* *
Help!
We're stuck on the roof
with no picnic!
Not no picnic.
I brought the napkins.
Never mind.
We have the napkins.
Help!
Don't--
I didn't say anything.
No!
(quietly):
I didn't say anything.
You said it with your eyes.
We can still do
the best part of a picnic...
sitting on the ground.
Carly, why don't you want people
to know about us?
Are you embarrassed
to be with me?
Oh, my God, no.
Not at all.
I'm obsessed with you.
When that fedora flew
off your head...
I was sad.
Look, I was in
a public relationship with Beau
and then he dumped me
during that live stream,
and the Internet piled on.
Guess I'm just worried
that if we go public,
I'll be opening you up
to that kind of pain.
Planning on dumping me
anytime soon?
No, of course not.
I just really want
to protect you.
I don't know if you know this,
but the Internet
can be kind of mean.
You don't have
to protect me, okay?
I can take whatever
they throw at us.
Or we can keep it
a secret forever.
It doesn't matter.
I just want to be with you.
You are everything
I have ever wanted,
and there's nothing that anyone
on the Internet could ever say
to make me feel differently.
Because I love you, Carly.
I'm in love with you.
Thank God I brought
these napkins.
(phone chimes)
Someone's finally
answering my texts.
It's my mom.
"FYI, your camera is on.
And it's not a flattering angle
for Carly's chin."
I started streaming
to show the drones
and completely forgot.
Hey...
(camera beeps)
Wow, these comments are
surprisingly nice.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
"It's about time."
"I want what you have."
"This is blowing my mind.
I'm definitely not clicking away
as fast as humanly possible."
-Aw...
-I think they're being
sarcastic.
Aw.
Screw the bubble.
I want the world to know.
(camera beeps)
I love you, Freddie Benson.
(buzzing)
The drones.
I guess destroying
the transmitter didn't work.
But they're making
some kind of picture.
Yeah, they're spelling out
"Creddie Forevvie"
-with a beating heart.
-Huh.
Doesn't really look
like a heart.
It's kind of weird, it-it looks
more like a microphone.
Yeah, or a horizontal
lighthouse.
I think I know what it is.
-It's a...
-Oh, no.
It's definitely not that.
Oh, yeah, I see it now.
The drones must have gone back
to their default formation.
But why would it be that?
Well, because probably
Spencer decided
to test the drones
by making a huge--
Oh, damn!
My lighthouse is on its side.
Can we just go back to you
telling me you love me?
Yeah, I thought you'd never ask.
I love you.
-Is it...
-Throbbing?
-Yep.
-Okay, now I really see it.
* *
Thanks for bringing champagne.
You didn't happen to see a sick
fedora on the street, did you?
-We'll get you a new one.
-(gasps)
And thanks for finally
rescuing us.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry I didn't hear my phone.
It was for totally
normal reasons.
Unrelated, does anyone know
where I can dump
a giant possum corpse?
Cheers to publicly
declaring your love.
-ALL: Cheers.
-Oh...
So that's where my chair is.
ALL:
No!
* *
Ooh!